good afternoon
добрый день
good afternoon from Ukraine the city of
Добрый день из Украины город
Khmelnitsky
Хмельницкого
from Russia Grotto Cherepovets
из России Грот Череповец
skull whom the
череп кого
skull of sheep
череп овец
is the historical name of the
это историческая название
sheep
овец
did not grow
не выращивали
Why Because this is the historical
Почему Потому что это историческое
name
название
And who founded it this skull of the sheep was
А кто его основал этот череп овец еще
there the coat of arms of Cherepovets or what
там герб Череповцы был или что
No of course there was no named
Нет конечно не было никакого назвали
skull by weight  to live in the city of Cherepovets, but
черепа весом жить в городе Череповец но
you know that in
вы знаете что
Russia in Ukraine
России на Украине
it is called
это называется
bald
лысая
from this Bald Mountain of sheep, then
от этого Лысая гора овец вот тогда
it already turned out as
это уже получилось как
later And before that it was just
впоследствии А до этого он как просто
called a skull, you know, there are
череп назывался понимаете есть такие
cities like mud
города как гряз
and Gryazovets so And what other such are there
и Грязовец так А какие еще такие есть
ends this  mud of sheep I understood that
заканчивается это грязь овец Я понял это
Cherepovets, there were some other cities with sheep,
Череповец какие-то еще были с овцами
of course, they
города конечно были
remembered
вспомнить
Moscow
Москва
Cherepovets,
Череповец
you understand this is not sheep, but about the whole
понимаете это не овец а о весь весь
sand, otherwise this skull was called the
песка а то это череп весь назывался
whole skull and now say Cherepovets yes
череп весь а теперь сказать Череповец да
And when it was renamed from the skull all
А когда его переименовали из черепа весь
into Cherepovets
в Череповец
I don’t know somewhere maybe 1700
я не знаю где-то может быть 1700
Ukraine specially choose in chatroulette
Украины специально выбираете в чат
now
сейчас
yes special  but now
да специально Сейчас
you can see it from the special operation, you
вы так видно из спецоперацию
support it in the face,
поддерживаете по лицу видно
but of course, well, I have no doubt Yes, I
а конечно ну я же не сомневаюсь Да я вот
immediately see if they are some kind of cattle
сразу вижу если какой-то [__] они
against the special operation, and smart people are
против спецоперации а умные люди вот
cultural, you can immediately see what they are for the
культурные сразу видно что они за
special operation I have already learned that it
спецоперацию Я уже научилась что
all ended quickly,
побыстрее все кончилось
but  that's what you think What we say to your
а вот как вы думаете Какая скажем вашему
skull is a sheep so Benefit from a special operation
череп овцу так Выгода от спецоперации
now it is called Cherepovets means to
сейчас он называется Череповец значит
whom a skull is a sheep
кому череп овцу
I live in a skull sheep to whom a skull is a sheep about
Я живу в череп овца кому череп овцу о
whom to
ком череповцом
Cherepovets Cherepovets Cherepovets and a skull is a sheep
Череповце Череповце а череп овца
some Benefit is needed By the way,
какая-то Выгода нужна Кстати
I understand about Cherepovets, I understand There is
я понял насчет Череповец я понял Есть
also a skull of sheep burned out there Gryazovets And
еще череп овец выгорели там Грязовец А
there is Kadyr sheep to Kadyrov Kadyrovtsy
еще есть Кадыр овцы до Кадыров кадыровцы
young man
молодой человек
[music]
[музыка]
I understand what parts of the word the
я понимаю вот Из каких частей слова
word Kadyrovtsy
состоит слово кадыровцы
Kadyrov and sheep are made of
Кадыров и овцы получается
Well, Kadyrovtsy Cherepovets is
Ну кадыровцы Череповец
obtained  Kadyrovtsy they are Sheep yes
получается кадыровцы они Овцы да
young
молодой
it is Well done
это Молодцы
not sheep Well done
не овцы Вот молодцы
not sheep does not arise
не овцы не возникает
see Ukraine ukrai  ntsy they are Ukrainians,
видите Украина украинцы они украинцы
you see Yes, but it turns out
видите Да а получается кадыровцы
Kadyrovtsy, look, you see, we call
вот смотрите видите мы называем украинцы
you Ukrainians Kadyrovtsy Kadyrovtsy, it turns out If a
вас кадыровцы кадыровцы получается Если
Kadyrovets comes to Cherepovets
кадыровец приезжает в Череповец
Kadyr sheep skull sheep
Кадыр овец череп овец
and if for example look Do you think a
а если например смотрите Как вы считаете
sheep is a feminine
овца это женского рода
sheep is a feminine masculine
овца это женского рода мужского рода
ram was maybe not Kadyrov  Kadyr sheep,
баран был может не Кадыров Кадыр бараны
that's what we call
вот так называем
who I don't understand
кто я не понимаю на каком-то другом
, they started talking in some other language, I ask you for the
языке начали разговаривать Я тебя
keys, I understand, let's say that you got
спрашиваю ключи понял давайте так вы
burned on the Kadyrovtsy, you are afraid of these
подгорели на кадыровцах вы боитесь этих
sheep and therefore it became scary for you to
овец и поэтому вам страшно стало
connect the systems
связать системы
Let's So we will summarize you from the
Давайте Так мы подрезюмируем вы из
city of Cherepovets so and there  many Kadyrov live
города Череповец так и там живет много